<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Election Blog for Gov1347</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Election Blog for Gov1347</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 4: Incumbency</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-10-02-week-4-incumbancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-10-02-week-4-incumbancy/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post, I will evaluate my existing model with the inclusion of incumbency and expert rating data. I will also include a model to visualize how expert ratings compare to actual vote share outcomes in a particular given year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 3: Polling and Elections</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-09-25-week-3-polling-and-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-09-25-week-3-polling-and-elections/</guid>
      <description>This weeks blog post will focus on incorporating polling data to add into my existing predictive model that already includes economy variables to test to see how our predictions improve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2: The Economy and Elections</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-09-15-week-2-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-09-15-week-2-post/</guid>
      <description>This weeks blog post will focus on using the economy as a variable to predictive modeling for the upcoming election using past data such as the unemployment rate, GDP for each quarter, RDI, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1 Post</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-09-11-week-1-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-09-11-week-1-post/</guid>
      <description>Blog Post Due 9/15/22 This is my first weekly election blog posting for an ongoing assignment for the class Election Analytics at Harvard College with Professor Ryan Enos. Enjoy! :)
I will be using the visualization customization extension for this blog post and will use the resulting data to make a prediction about the upcoming 2022 midterm election.
create a map of Republican/Democrat voteshare margin by state in a year of your choice, create a map of Republican/Democrat voteshare margin by state and congressional district in 2014, label each state (e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
